that I've made 14 of these
and you've made three.
(knocking)
(Raj:)Hey. Where are the guys?
(Penny:)Oh, they went to the store
to get solder,
(Penny:)which is metal you melt
to make science things.
(Bernadette:)Since when
do you work on weekends?
(Raj:)I'm an astrophysicist.
(Raj:)The stars don't take a day off.
(Penny:)You were home alone
and had no one to play with?
(Raj:)Well, the cleaning lady was
there, but she doesn't like me.
(Raj:)You need any help?
(Bernadette:)Not with
Lightning McQueen here.
(Penny:)I think we're good.
(Raj:)Okay. That's cool.
(Raj:)I guess everybody's involved
in this project but me.
(Raj:)So... see ya.
(door shuts)
(Bernadette:)I feel bad.
(Bernadette:)Should we have asked him
to stay?
KOOTHRAPPALI (high-pitched):
Yes.
(Amy:)Will you please tell me
where we're going?
(Sheldon:)Sorry, you're on
a need-to-know basis.
(Amy:)I'm driving the car.
(Amy:)I need to know.